Ta-da!
You're being filmed!
I am!
How do I look?
I'm a zombie!
But this flower thing is cute!
It's amazing!
There's also a bear!
It's covered in blood!
Yay!
How was Halloween?
It's a month early.
What?
Yeah, it's a month early.
It's a little early.
Everyone was inspired by the pro.
Yeah, yeah.
So, zombies are like,
I'm going to make this kind of wound.
There are other types of wounds.
There are many types of wounds.
My mouth is open.
I don't want to do it.
It's amazing.
But I'm going to make it.
I'm going to make it.
Yeah.
Bye bye!
Kawaii
Sakura Mukai
Aruni Konishi
Mucu
insistent
Hiyobia
Open an album
methods
Made last fall
Don't make me laugh, I'm in a good mood
Let's go!
Tutturu tutturu tuttu
Departure!
Today, we had an autograph session at
Tsutaya Shibuya!
Yeah!
How was it?
Hiyori-san
Everyone was so busy going home from
work and school
So we were able to write a lot of
autographs!
Yeah!
Good job on your work and school!
Good job!
It was fun talking to you!
We talked so much that we got late!
Sorry!
I talked a lot too!
There were so many things we wanted to
talk about!
I'm not good at talking!
She's cute!
My ponytail is a bit short today.
Your hair is short.
And I have a sense of touch.
Which one do you like?
My sense of touch.
Please subscribe to my channel!
I want you to try this.
Put this on the vertical.
OK.
No, the other way.
Can I stand on this?
It's difficult.
Is it difficult?
Did you do it?
Yes, I did.
And put the silver on it.
Put the silver on it.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Shhh!
Bye-bye!
I look like a purple.
You do.
I look like a blue.
Bye-bye!
Can you hear me?
Yes.
I can't hear you.
I just want to talk to you.
What?
Bye-bye!
I'm going to the movie.
Hello.
Wait a minute.
Welcome.
Thank you.
I haven't seen you lately.
I'm going to the movie.
Thank you for your viewing.
Thank you. I love you.
The wind suits you.
This is definitely not good.
It's not cool.
My ears are going to burst.
It's good.
I'm shooting a video.
I'm shooting a scene of punching.
You're good at it.
I'm training it.
I'm going to continue.
Punch.
Hello, everyone.
Lock on to your heart. We are HAKIMIX.
I did it!
Hey, is the mic on?
Yes, it is!
It's a little lonely without music.
Thank you for coming to the release day
of the release event of A-MEX second
single, C-POP.
Thank you very much!
I'd like to talk about each of them one
by one.
This time, the Apex Second Single was
recorded in five songs.
For me, there were songs that were
really a dream, songs that I could stand
on.
I've been working hard to achieve my
goal, so I'm glad that everyone was
happy with me.
I'm really happy that you said a lot of
things like, I'll do my best. Thank you.
I'm still not good enough for everyone,
and there are still a lot of things I
have to work on.
But I'll do my best to sing and sing
and deliver my feelings to everyone.
Please continue to support me.
And I was really happy to be able to
get the second place with everyone.
Thank you everyone.
Thank you everyone for coming today.
I'm so happy to be ranked No.2 on the
Amex Second Single Coin Shape Up.
I'm so happy that each and every one of
you here is supporting us.
Thank you so much.
This No.2 is a great result.
I hope that we can continue to move
forward to a better future.
Do you like Tokusen?
Do you want to have the best live with
us?
Do you want to make a legendary live at
Nakano SunPlus?
Thank you very much. Please follow us
anywhere.
Thank you very much for today.
This time...
Thank you.
This time, I was very happy to receive
the second place in the Apex Second
Season.
I was very happy, so I proudly told my
mom that I was second place.
Then, she said she cried because she
watched the live stream.
I heard my mom crying and I almost
cried.
But my mom told me,
Until you become first place, you
should stop crying.
I will aim for the first place next
time and do my best.
But really, so many people came to the
release day,
despite the weekday.
I was really happy.
There is also Nakano-san Plaza.
We will do our best to continue to make
good progress.
I would be happy if you could follow
us.
And I would be happy if you could
forgive the new members.
Thank you very much for today.
Please be careful not to catch a cold.
First of all, thank you all for coming
today.
Thank you very much.
This was my second single.
I was able to receive the second place
in the Oricon Daily Ranking
with the lead song,
thanks to the promoters who supported
me.
Thank you very much.
I will continue to improve my skills.
I would like to make today's show a
turning point.
I would like to continue to connect
with the future
by holding Nakano Sun Plaza on December
21, 2019.
I will do my best, so please support
me.
Everyone, I know that we have been
given the 2nd place, but I still don't
feel it.
I feel it.
I'm telling everyone now. I feel it.
I feel it, and I don't know if I feel
it, but TokiSan is...
How do I say this? It's crazy. TokiSan
is going to be famous.
What should I do?
Will you continue to follow us?
Yes!
Thank you very much.
So, I really...
Ah, 2nd place.
I wonder if I'm not in the right frame.
I'm sorry.
I really want to thank you for giving
me 2nd place today.
Thank you very much.
I'm fine!
I'm a bit of a Cinderella.
I'm a Cinderella, so I'm a bit funny.
I don't think I'm a Cinderella.
I want to perform live with a lot of
fun and excitement.
I'll definitely show you a more
powerful side than last year.
I'm really sorry that the publicity
company that supports us is really in
the way.
Our story has just begun.
I think that there is no limit to the
possibilities and there is no limit to
the possibilities.
If you're with the publicity company
and the members,
we believe that we can definitely make
a big wall into a small wall.
So, please wait for us, Nakano-san and
Kuro-san!
Please watch it a lot!
I'll show you how to bloom, the big
petals
I'll run through it recklessly, always
I'll engrave the meaning deep in my
heart
It's really over, everyone, everyone,
it's about to collapse
If you're in love, shake up, shake up,
shake a lick, shake up
Aim for the weight, ring, sacre bleu
Lose weight, lose weight, lose weight,
don't lose your health
Let's go, do me, do me, yo! Do me, do
me, yo!
Don't show me your true feelings
Do me, do me, yo! Do me, do me, yo!
Don't make a fool of me, I'm in the
middle of a relationship